A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication FA241
Rockefeller Archive Center
- "IMMUNIZATION: Routine immunization for adults" Original Manuscript, 27:98, 1985 Nov. 22 (Box 684, Folder 2414)
- "IMMUNIZATION: Routine immunization for adults" Reprints, 27:98, 1985 Nov. 22 (Box 684, Folder 2415)
- "IMMUNIZATION: Routine immunization for adults" Reprints, 27:98, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 684, Folder 2416)
- "GROWTH HORMONE: Biosynthetic growth hormone" Consultants: ML Drafts, 27:101, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 684, Folder 2417)
- "GROWTH HORMONE: Biosynthetic growth hormone" Manufacturers' Replies, 27:101, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 684, Folder 2418)
- "GROWTH HORMONE: Biosynthetic growth hormone" Sources: "Check Copy" 27:101, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 684, Folder 2419)
- "GROWTH HORMONE: Biosynthetic growth hormone" Original Manuscript, 27:101, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 684, Folder 2420)
- "GROWTH HORMONE: Biosynthetic growth hormone" Reprints, 27:101, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 684, Folder 2421)
- "DIAGNOSTIC TESTS: Office test for serum theophylline" Consultants: ML Drafts, 27:102, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 685, Folder 2422)
- "DIAGNOSTIC TESTS: Office test for serum theophylline" Manufacturers' Replies, 27:102, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 685, Folder 2423)
- "DIAGNOSTIC TESTS: Office test for serum theophylline" Sources: "Check Copy" 27:102, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 685, Folder 2424)
- "DIAGNOSTIC TESTS: Office test for serum theophylline" Original Manuscript, 27:102, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 685, Folder 2425)
- "DIAGNOSTIC TESTS: Office test for serum theophylline" Reprints, 27:102, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 685, Folder 2426)
- "DIAGNOSTIC TESTS: Office test for serum theophylline" Reprints, 27:102, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 685, Folder 2427)
- "DIAGNOSTIC TESTS: Office test for serum theophylline" Advertising: Package Insert, 27:102, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 685, Folder 2428)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Captopril for mild to moderate hypertension" Consultants: ML Drafts, 27:103, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 685, Folder 2429)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Captopril for mild to moderate hypertension" Manufacturers' Replies, 27:103, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 685, Folder 2430)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Captopril for mild to moderate hypertension" Sources: "Check Copy", 27:103, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 685, Folder 2431)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Captopril for mild to moderate hypertension" Original Manuscript, 27:103, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 685, Folder 2432)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Captopril for mild to moderate hypertension" Reprints, 27:103, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 685, Folder 2433)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Captopril for mild to moderate hypertension" Reprints, 27:103, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 686, Folder 2434)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Captopril for mild to moderate hypertension" Advertising: Package Insert, 27:103, 1985 Dec. 20 (Box 686, Folder 2435)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE(Surgery): Antimicrobial prophylaxis for- surgery" Consultants: ML Drafts, 27:105, 1985 Dec. 20 (Box 686, Folder 2436)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE(Surgery): Antimicrobial prophylaxis for- surgery" Consultants: ML Drafts, 27:105, 1985 Dec. 20 (Box 686, Folder 2437)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE(Surgery): Antimicrobial prophylaxis for- surgery" Manufacturers' Replies, 27:105, 1985 Dec. 20 (Box 686, Folder 2438)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE(Surgery): Antimicrobial prophylaxis for- surgery" Sources: "Check Copy", 27:105, 1985 Dec. 20 (Box 686, Folder 2439)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE(Surgery): Antimicrobial prophylaxis for- surgery" Original Manuscript, 27:105, 1985 Dec. 20 (Box 686, Folder 2440)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE(Surgery): Antimicrobial prophylaxis for- surgery" Reprints, 27:105, 1985 Dec. 20 (Box 686, Folder 2441)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE(Surgery): Antimicrobial prophylaxis for- surgery" Reprints, 27:105, 1985 (Box 687, Folder 2442)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Drugs of choice from- The Medical Letter" Asthma, (Bin 1), Rv. Ed., 1985 (Box 687, Folder 2443)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Drugs of choice from- The Medical Letter" Asthma, (Bin 1), Rv. Ed., 1985 (Box 687, Folder 2444)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Drugs of choice from- The Medical Letter" Epilepsy, (Bin 1), Rv. Ed., 1985 (Box 687, Folder 2445)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Drugs of choice from- The Medical Letter" Original Manuscript, (Bin 1), Rv. Ed., 1985 (Box 687, Folder 2446)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Drugs of choice from- The Medical Letter" Psychiatric drugs, (Bin 1), Rv. Ed., 1985 (Box 687, Folder 2447)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Drugs of choice from- The Medical Letter" Psychiatric drugs, (Bin 1), Rv. Ed., 1985 (Box 687, Folder 2448)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Drugs of choice from- The Medical Letter" Arrhythmias, (Bin 2), Rv. Ed., 1985 (Box 688, Folder 2449)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Drugs of choice from- The Medical Letter" Arrhythmias (Bin 2), Rv. Ed., 1985 (Box 688, Folder 2450)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Drugs of choice from- The Medical Letter" Arrhythmias, (Bin 2), Rv. Ed., 1985 (Box 688, Folder 2451)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Drugs of choice from- The Medical Letter" Back up, (Bin 2), Rv. Ed., 1985 (Box 688, Folder 2452)
- "ERYTHROMYCIN: Additional Note" Consultants: ML Drafts, not published, 1985 (Box 688, Folder 2453)
- "ERYTHROMYCIN: Additional Note" Manufacturers' Replies, not published, 1985 (Box 688, Folder 2454)
- "ERYTHROMYCIN: Additional Note" Original Manuscript, not published, 1985 (Box 688, Folder 2455)
- "ERYTHROMYCIN: Additional Note" Reprints, not published, 1985 (Box 688, Folder 2456)